<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Top Places App</string>

    <string name="cairns">Cairns and Great Barrier Reff Regions</string>
    <string name="sydney">Sydney</string>
    <string name="uluru">Uluru</string>
    <string name="melbourne">Melbourne</string>
    <string name="perth">Perth</string>
    <string name="kangaroo">Kangaroo Island</string>
    <string name="kakadu">Kakadu</string>
    <string name="hobart">Hobart</string>
    <string name="goldcoast">Gold Coast</string>
    <string name="byronbay">Byron Bay</string>

    <string name="cairns_desc">Byron Bay</string>
    <string name="sydney_desc">Australia’s largest city is one of the world’s prettiest. Much of its allure revolves around the harbour, a dramatic expanse that creates a sanctuary for some of the country’s best beaches. This is the Sydney you see on postcards, with the immense Harbour Bridge and shell-like fans of the Opera House skirting the emerald waters. More sandy stretches await along the coast, from Coogee to Bondi, attracting surfers and sun-worshippers alike. </string>
    <string name="uluru_desc">This huge red monolith is a World Heritage site, and one of Australia’s most emblematic landmarks. Uluru is literally the heart of Australia, and the ochre soil is as dramatic as the massive sandstone rock itself. You can cycle, walk, ride a camel or take a helicopter around the nearly 10-kilometre (6.2-mile) circumference, then dine under the stars on a sand dune – your meal featuring native ingredients and your view lit by an incredible glowing art installation: Bruce Munro’s Field of Light.</string>
    <string name="melbourne_desc">This southern metropolis captures everything Aussies love most in this world – leisure, sport, art, music and coffee (just to name a few). In Melbourne, you can find eye-popping street art and a plethora of en vogue restaurants and bars. From hidden speakeasies to rooftop bars where you can sip a cocktail and watch the sunset, Melbourne is a trailblazer in the food and wine stakes. Once you\'ve wined and dined, you can’t miss a road trip along the Great Ocean Road. Just a few hours from Melbourne, wild koalas, impressive rock formations and endless coastlines await.</string>
    <string name="perth_desc">Australia’s western capital is the gateway to some of the state’s most epic adventures – not least those involving food and wine. It’s a three-hour drive from Perth to the Margaret River region, one of the few places in the world where wine grows within metres of the beach. The vineyards here are known for their cabernet sauvignon grapes, but take it from us, all the wines grown here are exquisite. There’s also a myriad of craft breweries, acclaimed restaurants, luxury hotels, spectacular forests and plenty to keep the kids entertained.</string>
    <string name="kangaroo_desc">This secluded island off the coast of South Australia is named after the (you guessed it) abundant local kangaroo species. But Kangaroo Island offers more than just ‘roos’! The island is a haven for all kinds of Australian flora and fauna. Think koalas, sea lions, echidnas, wallabies and dolphins – just to name a few. You’ll also discover an extraordinary array of breathtaking landscapes – cosy coves, towering trees and remarkable rock formations. When you’re done marvelling at nature, you can retire to the charming towns to enjoy a glass of locally produced wine paired with fine produce grown on the island’s farms.</string>
    <string name="kakadu_desc">World Heritage-listed Kakadu National Park offers a front-row seat to the dramatic wilderness of the Northern Territory. The park is a three-hour drive from the capital city of Darwin and when you arrive, you’ll find woodlands, floodplains, mangroves, tidal mudflats and even monsoon forest. Stay overnight and see landscapes ranging from thundering waterfalls to rocky gorges. If you want a place to feel completely insignificant – in the best possible way – Kakadu awaits.</string>
    <string name="hobart_desc">Located on the island state of Tasmania, Hobart is the perfect place to pause, reconnect and take a breath of some of the freshest air in the world. Visitors can get a taste of the things that make Australia great, from fine dining and cultural attractions to stunning natural beauty. There\'s an endless parade of outdoor activities within reach of the city: epic alpine mountaineering, ocean kayaks and World Heritage-listed hikes. After a breathtaking adventure, reward yourself with the tastes of Tasmania at Hobart’s best restaurants or enjoy some locally brewed beverages at the irresistible bar offerings.  </string>
    <string name="goldcoast_desc">If the Gold Coast enjoys a sparkling reputation, it\'s because there are 300 days of sunshine here every year. This golden city unites the things that make this country great: beautiful beaches, a blissful tropical climate, world-class restaurants and bars, and easy access to tangles of rainforest – you can be surfing one minute, then trekking half an hour later. The ‘Goldie’ is also home to a parade of theme parks and attractions, promising endless days of action and adventure for the whole family. </string>
    <string name="byronbay_desc">There’s a reason why Nicole Kidman, Chris Hemsworth and Simon Baker (along with thousands of other lucky Aussies) call Byron Bay home – it really is one of Australia’s most beautiful coastal coves. Nestled on the coast of northern New South Wales, Byron is tipped by a picturesque hilltop lighthouse (the mainland\'s most easterly point). In the town’s centre, you can get a tarot reading, take a surfing lesson, indulge in paddock-to-plate meals, or simply sip a local brew while spotting dolphins and watching whales on their annual migration. </string>
</resources>